

EMRE KARA

SR. FRONTEND DEVELOPER

CONTACT

Email

emrekara.dev@gmail.com

Phone

+90 551 101 4100

GitHub

github.com/emrekaraa

Website

emrekara.dev

Linkedin

linkedin.com/in/emrekaraa

Address

Cekmekoy / Istanbul / Turkey

LANGUAGES

Turkish

Native Language

English

B1 - Intermediate Level

REFERENCES

Ahmet Eren Ozturkmen

Co-Founder - Tamer Capital Phone: +90 507 433 96 63

Atakan Yurttutan

Team Lead - Yenibiris Phone: +90 553 324 99 52

EDUCATION

Web Design and Coding

Ataturk Univercity
Associate Degree - Continues

Faculty Of Theology

Anadolu Univercity
Associate Degree - Graduate

ABOUT ME

I have 3+ years experience in Frontend Development especially React.js and Next.js. I describe myself as a JavaScript developer, not a framework developer. I like to try and learn new technologies. I'm a self-taught learner. I'm passionate about my work. Because I love what I do. I have a steady source of motivation that drives me to do my best.

EXPERIENCE

06/2023 - Now

Present

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Demirören Holding / Yenibiris

D

I am working on the Yenibiris.com website renewal project. I am also developed an online interview exam project.

11/2022 - 06/2023

8 Months

sodex*o

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Sodexo

I have worked on a back office web application used by Sodexo call center users. I am also developed the Sodexo Mobile App and Sodexo Cep Pos App.

10/2022 - 11/2022

2 Months



FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Sigma Group

I made the backend and frontend of the kocyasa.com website. I also developed a content management system for the project.

08/2021 - 10/2022

1 Year 2 Months



FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Tamer Capital

I have worked on multiple projects at the same time. I made web applications, admin panels, official websites and many reusable components.

SOFTWARE SKILLS

- Frontend
 - JavaScript TypeScript React.js React Native Next.js
- Backend
 - Node.js Express.js MongoDb PostgreSql
- Devops
- Linux Shell Aws Cloud NginX Docker CI-CD Pipeline
- Others
 - Postman Git Jira Figma AdobeXD PhotoShop